<xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"><news><title>Modern Warfare 3 Patch beseitigt Glitches und Bugs</title><content>Mit dem neusten Update für Call of Duty: Modern Warfare 3 werden erneut die Waffen neu balanciert und einige Bugs gefixt. Zudem gibt der Entwickler Infinity Ward einen Ausblick auf kommende Patches und DLC’s. Doch neben den Waffen wurden unter anderem auch einige Karten geändert, um zu verhindern, dass Spieler Zugagng zu orten haben die nicht vorgesehen waren (So genannte Glitches). In einem zukünfigen Update sollen dann noch die Schrotgewehre angepasst werden, da diese momentan noch mehr Kugeln verschießen als geplant. Der Patch steht seit heute zum Download bereit, und wird wie gewohnt automatisch von Steam installiert.

[VMP] Behemoth

Das komplette Changelog gibt es hier:

Hot Fix Updates (Released):
- No Recoil glitch
- Infinite Laptop killstreak glitch (Stealth Bomber Glitch)
- Map Exploits (Getting into trucks, under maps) Fix
- Prevent Slow-mo and Super Fast lobbies
- Hot Fix Updates (Releasing Today 12/12/11):
- Fire rate normalization for Assault Rifles with undermounts
- FMG9 Re-balancing (Nerf)
- Akimbo FMG9 Re-balancing (Nerf)
- Type95 Re-balancing (Nerf) - Reduce hipspread.
- Fix for ACR with Red Dot / Shotgun
- Fix Type 95 bug related to dropping it.
- Fix map exploits on Dome
- Re-balancing and Updates currently in Development and/or Discussion:

Updates to the Spawn system
- Further “lag compensation” or “host advantage / disadvantage” updates plus ability for on-going hot fixes based on feedback.
- Fix for Shotgun’s with Extended Mags (Prevents them from shooting more pellets than intended)
- Default :30 Round Start timer for System Link only, while looking into adjustable timer for System Link games for Competitive Play.
- Options to allow System Link players to ‘unlock all’ for competitive play in System Link only.</content><author>Behemoth</author><game>CallOfDutyModernWarfare3</game><source></source><year>2011</year><month>12</month><day>13</day><time>17:07</time></news>